Thank you for watching.
Now then, Mr. Nogi, Koji, here is your host, Bananaman. Let me send you the schedule.
Good luck, Mr. Nogi!
Good luck, good luck, banana, good luck, good luck.
Oh, what?
There it is!
It's Daikichi.
That's Shokichi.
He's sitting in a very nice chair, isn't he?
It's a little embarrassing.
You've seen him before.
You know something about him, don't you?
Mr. Himura, please announce what we're doing today.
Here we go.
Shokichi's male appearance.
What's this?
He won the rock-paper-scissors battle.
Sugawara won a prize of white goods at the darts tournament.
He's decided to go on a shopping location with Bananaman.
The members who could accompany Sugawara on location were the top 7 people who won the game Sugawara wanted to play.
Only the top 7 people who won the game Sugawara wanted to play and got Shokichi points
The number of people who can ride in that car is about seven.
Well, if it's already just barely 8 or so, I might make it 8.
I'll bring 7 people with me.
Basically, you have to give Shokichi a great deal of credit for that location.
That's right.
So, hey...
A little bit...
Yes, he's cute. He's a real little fish.
You're a real fish... But it's important...
You do it even when the camera's off. That's what I'm talking about.
Please do.
Nakanishi is nodding his head so much. Can you do it?
Can you do it, Nakanishi? I'll do it.
Give it a try.
Please, Mr. Meal.
So this is how it's going to be, Mr. Meal.
Let's get right to it. What's first?
Non-star derby.
I wasn't in the studio for this one.
I wasn't there.
I wasn't there, but I'm more on the smelly side.
I just wanted to play.
The game Sugawara chose was the luggage-carrying race that we played in the Don Smell Derby.
You had to efficiently move all of the various pieces of luggage
The contestants compete to see how long it takes to efficiently move all of the various items on the table to the other side of the table.
This time, the member who beats Sugawara's time will win a point.
There are four members participating, including Sugawara.
Have you done this before, Ichinose?
I've never done it.
You don't look like a stinker.
He's firm.
Strong-willed.
Tomisato doesn't look so smelly either.
He's confident.
And... Here comes our champion, Nakanishi!
The queen.
JoOusama has experience.
Queen is back...
And I've been trying to be very agile since then.
I'm fine.
She's also very quick when she carries things from one place to another.
Yes, really.
That's good. I'm glad the project is working for you.
I think she might have lied.
First, Ichinose vs. Tomisato, our first challenge.
You and Nakanishi must be blindfolded.
I'll be careful.
You're doing that already?
Yes.
You know what I'm talking about.
I thought you didn't.
I used to sneak a peek or something.
Nakanishi.
That's why you lost.
huh?
You seem like a small fish.
Ichinose Tomisato.
It's the way you carry it. You have to think about it.
You're not supposed to drink this kind of stuff.
Definitely.
It's okay.
You don't mind?
Yes, it's okay.
Won't that take a while?
No.
And you're going to carry it?
No, not that one.
I was about to do it. Not this one, but this one?
This is fine.
If you drink it, you have to serve it at the finish line.
No, no, no, no...
Let's go! First round!
Let's go!
Go for it.
Not so slow.
You're going at a nice pace.
Amazing.
We're both...
You're so smart.
There's more than one of them.
Oh, my God.
Let's drop it.
He's down, he's down!
It's his head!
Please, please, please!
Tomisaka, who started off at a leisurely pace, making tanka poems with a tank top... and Ichinose, who made a big tray out of a tank top and flaflops.
Ichinose made a big tray with a tank top and flaflops.
This time, they started the game with a brainy strategy!
Falling Falling Falling Falling
Fall, fall, fall
Tough.
From there, from there, from there...
What do you think of that?
That's really harsh.
Now logr
Tomisato's legalized water-drinking strategy.
And Ichinose's Santa Claus strategy of using them as sock bags
It's down, it's down, it's down, it's down
It's down, it's down, it's down
Down, down, down, down!
Back, back, back!
Under unusually severe conditions
Tomisato, who was led by Ichinose who repeatedly used the tray
Tomisato, who was leading Ichinose who repeatedly used the tray, tried to regain the lead by coming up with a strategy to make efficient progress.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Wow!
You're not straddling!
I'm not straddling you!
Tomisato, I'm not straddling you right now!
I made a mistake!
I made a mistake.
The current one.
The one now... with the top...
No, no, no!
The top and the rope.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Tomisato lost a lot of time due to the panic of forgetting to straddle the bar.
Tomisato lost a lot of time because he forgot to straddle the bar.
Ichinose carried all the luggage
and went ahead of the others!
That's right... candy, candy, candy... roll!
That's why we lost an ameam, ameam, and an egg!
Ito and Misato also made it to the finish line with Referee Himura!
Next up, the Donkusa queens Nakanishi and Sugawara face off!
Let's go!
Let's get started!
It's the same start, isn't it?
Exactly the same.
It's like looking in a mirror.
It's on! It's on!
If you drop it, you have to do it again.
How do you get over it?
The two of them had a similar start.
Sugawara steadily carrying sweets on a paper plate.
Nakanishi, on the other hand, stacked cups of water on top of each other
I'm nervous.
I'm a little nervous if I spill it.
water spills.
water water water
Water water water water
Water's spilling. - Water's spilling.
Water spilling.
Water!
Nakanishi... water you spilled.
Please don't fall and hit the outside and die.
That's what I mean.
Take your time.
Yes! Yes!
There you go! That's it! That's it! That's it!
That's it! That's it!
Seriously?
Oh, come on!
It's garbage! Garbage!
Garbage! Garbage!
Come on! Come on!
Miho! Miho!
What's wrong?
Let the sound inside reach you!
Come on! Come on, you guys!
Come on! Come on!
It looked like Yasukawa was never going to win.
But that didn't stop Nakanishi from running amok.
Don't spill, Strongest
I slipped, I slipped, I dropped, I dropped.
Are you okay?
Sugawara was first to the finish line.
Don't you have any more pockets?
The Donksa queens continued to show their superiority by dominating the field.
And finally, they reach the finish line!
Fast forward to the end.
Here are the three's times.
Sugawara's time was
4 minutes and 56 seconds.
That was first place.
First place!
We did it!
There was no winner, so it was only Ichinose who was the fastest.
That was really bad, Nakanishi!
I'm really shocked.
But I think I've lost that kind of laziness.
Where?
What will be the next initial test?
Speed Queen Showdown
This is also Shokichi's favorite project in the past.
When the subject is announced, episode talk and mimicry are performed by a quick push.
This time, if you answer twice before Sugawara, you get 1 Shokichi point!
You'd better push it.
You have to keep pushing this one too.
Interference is not allowed.
Of course you can't interfere.
They're going to interfere?
Of course not!
First, let's have a quick push episode talk showdown among the five of us!
Thank you for your hard work!
Let's go!
Here's the subject.
I got it!
Who is it?
Oh, my God!
Recently...
I asked the hairdresser to trim the ends of my hair a little bit.
I was surprised to find out that she cut off about 5cm of my hair, and now every time I see her she asks me if I cut off my hair.
Oh!
Well, it's okay, it's quick.
Well, it's not funny at all, but it's okay.
It's not so much the quality, but the speed... the speed is good, and the size is good.
I think that's the standard.
Oh!
I can't give it to you in that sense, but...
IkedaIf you get the next one, you get one more point.
It doesn't have to be fun.
It's okay.
That's the standard.
Guts is important.
It's okay.
Let's move on to the next subject.
Who is it?
Myself.
I'm proud of myself.
Recently
I went to pick out furisode (long-sleeved kimono)
Wow!
And I tried on a lot of different ones.
I'm proud of the fact that the person wearing the kimono told me that I looked good in all of them because of my long neck!
Oh, that's nice!
Yes, OK.
That's great.
If you have a long neck, you'll be reflected in the back.
Good for you.
That's a long neck.
It's long.
It is long, but...
I'd like to wear it with a lot of rings.
That's nice.
This one, this one.
I like this one.
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go, Shokichi is pushing too hard
No, he's pushing, but he's simply losing.
Okay, here's the next subject
I'm going to go for it!
Here you go.
When I made the plastic model, I used nippers...
If you use nippers to remove this nail...
If you remove this skin-like thing, it becomes very beautiful.
Heh...
It's the cuticle.
Cuticle.
That's a great one.
I don't know if this is a good idea.
It's not good.
It's pretty clean if you use your own judgment.
It's gonna be beautiful. Oh, that's great.
That's great. - That's great.
That's great. That's great.
Let's go for it. Next subject, this way
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch
This is a story about how we got lucky.
Yoda... please.
I was eating horse meat yesterday and got some sauce on the paper.
But right at that moment... he brought me a hand towel.
Is that lucky?
It was a mistake, but at that very moment, he brought me a hand towel shell.
So I could blow it right away.
You didn't tell her you were coming?
I didn't tell him.
Is that what you call lucky?
No.
Let's go. Next subject.
This way.
Aki-San, Kanagawa.
Tamura's here. Let's go.
I went home the other day.
And...
I hadn't been home for a while, so my mom was very excited.
She served my favorite dishes, grilled shrimp, fried chicken and beef tongue, and I was so full.
It's so comforting.
It's nice, isn't it? It's so dusty.
I'm so relieved.
You're lucky with this theme, aren't you?
This is...
It's a great theme.
Here we go.
Next subject.
This way.
Here it comes.
What?
Shokichi's story.
Shokichi's story
That's what Ikeda said.
But it's the same.
It's a good omen. Let's go.
There's a cute little baby stingray...
A baby stingray. I'm addicted to it.
We've been imitating baby stingray faces.
What do you think? Let's see.
Aww...
Aww.
It's okay. It's okay.
How is it? It's fine.
It's fine, but what is this, Mr. Ishida?
Oh, nothing. It's just that...
All right, but that's not what I'm talking about.
It's OK.
You get one point.
Ikeda got one point.
And here's the next score.
He's gone! Oops! You're early! Let's talk about what's been irritating you lately!
I'm annoyed with myself, but I told you about the horse meat just now, didn't I?
There was more.
There was more?
When I went to Hong Kong for a concert...
There was a concert in Hong Kong recently, wasn't there?
I went to the bathroom and dropped my phone in the toilet.
Oh!
And it's gone! I thought, "What should I do?
I thought it must be gone, so I went to the information desk, and it was there.
Oh!
They told me I was lucky.
I was annoyed that I couldn't say that.
You're good.
That's good.
Good job with the phone.
The way you're doing it now, technically.
That's pretty hard to do.
I think it's a great technique.
If you do this all the time, you can really train it.
It's amazing!
That's all for now.
The winners were Yoda and Ikeda. Next, the five of us changed the subject to mimicry and tried our hand at it.
I did an impersonation of Haruna Kondo, and she saw me do it.
When we were together on the show, she said I looked like that.
Do you remember how you did it again?
May I have some? Here you go.
It's not Shrek.
What are you doing?
It's speed.
What's going to happen next? Is this going to turn the industry upside down?
Let's start with the genre.
Entertainers!
It's too fast!
This is terrible.
Who do we have for you?
Here we go.
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
I don't know what he's thinking.
Let's go!
This is a genre.
I'm in female vomit!
Who is it?
It's Yumiki!
This is the person who will do it.
Yasuko.
Here we go
Three, two, one...
Go ahead.
I'm Yasuko, from the Self-Defense Forces.
Here you go.
Oh!
Congratulations!
But aren't you trying to be a little cute?
Maybe a little more high.
I'd do the cheek crumbs if it was something like that.
I don't mind if you do.
If you say it yourself...
Well, that's okay.
Okay, here are the genres.
Male Performing Arts
This is persimmon.
This is Takeshi-san.
Takeshi-san.
321, please.
Kodauchi.
You've gone all out, haven't you?
We're lucky to have someone who has one of these.
It's lucky.
Let's go.
This way.
Female entertainer.
There she is.
It's Yumiki.
Yumiki, you get a point for this.
Who'll it be?
Let's go with Ano!
What shall we do?
321, go ahead.
Say it!
What was that?
Not at all.
Oh, come on, keep going.
I wish I could take it back.
Did you say you were listening to music today?
I did.
I don't know why you're being such a pussy.
But you're funny as hell.
I don't have to say anything like that.
Should I have said my name first?
Um...
You don't look anything like him!
Not at all.
Say more!
Aren't you going slowly?
Um...
Today...
Yesterday?
Yes, OK.
Okay.
Come on, this way.
Oh, here they come!
Yes, Kubo!
Who is it? This way!
Yes, it's Ayu!
Three, two, one!
It's Ayu!
It's IKKO, IKKO!
It's Ayu! Gals! Everyone's a gal!
OK, OK!
OK, OK, OK, OK!
You wouldn't say that, would you?
But okay.
But what?
I just now...
Next, Shimura Ken with a quick push of the persimmon.
Here you go.
Aiin...
Okay.
Okay...
It's the only way to do it.
Kaki is doing "ai" with the komaneci.
That's great.
They're doing a double application gag.
You should tell Ogawa.
Let's go to Ogawa.
This way, please.
Who the hell's Ogawa?
Ogawa-kun.
Male comedian!
Who will it be?
Hollywood Zacochon.
Three, two, one. Go ahead.
Hamburger steak.
Here we go.
No way.
No way. No way.
Who's number one?
The hamburger market, I see.
That's the hamburger market.
It's Mr. Itoda.
That's right.
Let's go on with the next one.
Oh, I fell.
It's down.
Who's going to do it?
Mr. Degawa, let's go.
Three, two, one.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no!
What did you say, Mr. Degawa?
This is terrible.
Yes, it's no good.
This is terrible!
No, no, no. We talked about this earlier.
What did you say about Mr. Degawa?
No, no, he's good.
It's no good.
How did we do that?
Here we go. Three, two, one.
Oh, no, no, no, it hurts too much to hold this crawfish by the nose.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
You talk a lot. I knew it.
Yeah, I know.
It's good to talk a lot.
You've got to say things like, "Oh, no!" and "Crayfish!
That's a good one.
So, those who got points for mimicry right away were...
Kubo, Kaki, and Yumiki.
I guess it's a game meal to follow
Tiki meal
Sudo says he's good at playing the game of guessing what you ate by playing IASCO.
So, what was in the program's special mixed juice?
You will be asked to guess what are the 5 kinds of vegetables and fruits in the mixed juice specially made for the program.
Here are the five who will take on the challenge.
I'm sure you're good at cooking, though.
But in most of these things, there's one strong one and then there's the rest, so that's what I'm worried about.
The rest are left over, so I'm a little nervous.
I see.
You're right.
You've got it all figured out.
What about Endo?
Did I miss something?
I wonder.
But even if I did, I think he'd change if I blindfolded him.
That's true.
I wouldn't know if he pinched my nose.
But if you were blindfolded, you could only taste it.
Would you be able to tell?
What about good?
I don't know what "good" means.
But, sir...
You were talking like you're really good at it.
But I don't think you're good at it.
That's right.
You just have to beat Soki.
No, no, no...
Inoue?
My tongue.
Tongue.
It's so stupid.
Then it's no good.
That's why you're not good at this game.
Most things taste better if you put them in your mouth.
That's not true.
Well then, here you go...
So all five of us tasted the pineapple at once.
I'm fine with the aroma.
Who is this?
This is Shokichi
It's Shokichi, isn't it?
Shokichi
This is Shokichi
What is this?
There are 5 kinds
Vegetables
Fruits
Oh!
It's that plum.
I keep forgetting with that face.
I said I'd forget.
All right, then.
Can the five of you guess what's inside?
Let's start with Inoue.
Open.
Apples, oranges, carrots...
Tomatoes. None.
None?
It's got that rough texture.
I thought apples would be like that in a smoothie.
I thought bananas would be thicker.
Cheerful?
Yes, sir.
What? Banana? Please announce.
The first time I changed the scent, I felt banana.
I only have Inoue and orange in my head.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Let's end with something I thought might be in there.
Banana, apple, kiwi, komatsuna, mango...
If they put komatsuna, I wouldn't know.
I cut a banana on the first shot.
Oh, bananas?
It was so strong, I couldn't tell what else was there.
You wrote "banana" too.
I felt it the first time.
Let's go, Plum.
Let's go.
Celery, apple, banana, pineapple, peach...
Celery... No, but...
No one else has celery. Celery is very strong.
I'm confident about celery, apple and banana.
The aroma is banana.
And when I drank it, I tasted the apple, and I thought the celery was in the back.
Celery is hidden.
Celery?
It didn't smell too green, so I'm guessing it's not the only vegetable.
Maybe not. I don't know.
Okay, let's keep going, Don.
Tomatoes, strawberries, kiwis, grapes, carrots.
Oh, he put tomatoes in.
But they're all different.
For the record, Mr. Himura also participated. His answer.
Yes, Don.
Apples, carrots, strawberries, garlic, onions.
No onions.
It's a little pungent, a little spicy.
Apple, carrot, too. It's confirmed.
There's no banana in this.
Oh, no...
I wonder if any of these answers are correct.
Apple, banana, tomato, celery, ginger...
So...
The number of correct answers is the number of points from Sugawara, so Umezawa has 2 base points for winning.
Endo and Inoue won one base point.
How can you not understand this?
I don't get it at all.
You don't know how to do it, do you?
I didn't understand the ginger.
If you say so, I'll say sure.
It's ginger now!
It's definitely ginger!
That's why it's garlic and onions... in my mind.
Ah...
That's why Iyoki, Himura and Shokichi have such stupid tongues, don't they?
Tickets for the Tokyo show streaming viewing are now on sale!
Good evening, I'm Hazuki Mukai. I went to buy some gifts for the members yesterday, but I didn't have enough money to buy them, so I'll be back tomorrow.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Please subscribe to our channel!